<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetadata xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <Name>FPGA [StationeersMods]</Name>
  <Author>tom_is_unlucky</Author>
  <Version>0.1.2</Version>
  <!-- Steam description using steam styling tags for Steam workshop page -->
  <Description>[h1]FPGA[/h1]
    [b]WARNING:[/b] This is a StationeersMods Plugin Mod. It requires Bepinex to be installed with the StationeersMods plugin.
    See: https://jixxed.github.io/StationeersMods/

    The FPGA mod lets you replace a big pile of logic devices with one configurable chip. Connect it with a few Logic Readers and Writers to automate your base, or access it with IC10 chips for fast reusable computation. The chips are easily configurable with the form or text based editors.

    In contrast to IC10 chips, which execute instructions one at a time, FPGA chips run all configured gates simultaneously, allowing you to just change the inputs and immediately read the new outputs. This allows a single FPGA chip to calculate results multiple times per tick when accessed from one or even multiple IC10 chips.

    [h2]New Items:[/h2]

    [h3]ItemFPGAChip[/h3]
    Simple FPGA-like chip with 64 input pins, 64 gates, and 64 lookup table values.

    [h3]ItemKitFPGAHousing[/h3]
    Kit to construct housings to hold FPGA chips.

    [h3]StructureFPGALogicHousing[/h3]
    Chip housing that allows full access to all inputs/outputs of FPGA chip.
    Requires get/getd/put/putd instructions from IC10 chips.

    [h3]StructureFPGAReaderHousing[/h3]
    Chip housing that allows connecting first 8 inputs to data network devices and outputs first 8 gate values as logic values.
    Can be connected to logic devices to automate calculations without IC10.

    [h3]MotherboardFPGA[/h3]
    Motherboard that provides a form and text editor for FPGA configuration.
    Use a computer (not laptop) to import/export to FPGA chips in housings.

    Check the stationpedia pages and editor motherboard for more details.
  </Description>
  <!-- Ingame Description using TMP tags for Workshop menu -->
  <InGameDescription>
    <![CDATA[<size="30"><color=#ffa500> FPGAMod </color></size>
<b>WARNING:</b> <color=#ff0000>This is a StationeersMods Plugin Mod. It requires Bepinex to be installed with the StationeersMods plugin.</color>
See: https://jixxed.github.io/StationeersMods/

Adds a basic FPGA chip, housings and editor motherboard, printable from electronics printer.
]]>
  </InGameDescription>
  <!-- All contents of ChangeLog should be changed for each publication for Steam workshop page -->
  <ChangeLog>
    [h3]Version 0.1.2:[/h3]
    [list]
    [*]Fix error when running a freshly printed chip
    [/list]
  </ChangeLog>
  <WorkshopHandle>3457324551</WorkshopHandle>
  <!-- StationeersMods and BepInEx tags for Steam workshop page will be automatically added by the framework when publishing -->
  <Tags>
    <Tag>StationeersMods</Tag>
  </Tags>
  <!-- Automatic downloads of dependencies -->
  <Dependencies />
  <!-- Automatic reordering of the mods list -->
  <LoadBefore />
  <LoadAfter />
</ModMetadata>
